Skills are awesome.
But there's an irony to them.
They're built to be reusable,
but they don't actually have a distribution system.
So what people end up doing is they're copying down these markdown
files and folders, and they're checking them into their repos
and sometimes even multiple times within the same repo,
because they want different agents to consume them.
Ah, that’s the worst, when there's so much sprawl across a number of different
repos, there's, you know, stale skills hanging around, not getting updates.
It's terrible what you're essentially saying is
we need a kind of package manager to organize this. Precisely.
You know, we've solved this problem in software.
We know that we can package them up. We can version them.
We can build manifest files that track what you have installed.
These are solved problems.
We just haven't solved them from skills.
But what did Tessl release?
How can Tessl help with this problem?
So Tessl launched a package manager for skills and other types of context.
We help you install skills.
You can install any skill from any GitHub
repo and such, but it will install it via the registry.
And we will keep a manifest file that remembers what you have installed.
And it gives you actions like, you know, updating them over time.
You can track them.
It doesn't duplicate content in your system,
just like a proper professional developer grade package manager would do.
So I'm a heavy skills user today.
How can I use Tessl to to discover new skills,
but also use my existing skills that I have in my system today?
So to consume skills you just install the Tessl CLI from npm.
And you can run Tessl install of any skill or Tessl skill search
if you want to find others.
And once you've done it, you'll have a manifest file.
It'll be there.
You can continue to action it.
You can also check out the registry to find the evaluations
of these different skills so you can pick the better ones.
If you are creating skills, then you can publish skills
to the registry through again CLI actions that should feel very natural.
And then you can use those and manage them in workspaces
to distribute them across your team with the right access controls.
Amazing.
So if I'm a publisher, I can actually create and share skills
for myself, others in the community as well as in my organization.
Precisely.
And it will even run those evaluations for you when you publish.
Amazing.
So now I know where my skills are and also whether they're any good or not.
Precisely. Amazing.
So if you are using skills
or your producing skills, head over to tessl.io/registry,
where you can publish skills that you and your organization use,
as well as discover
other skills from the community that you can download and use today.